(instrumental music plays)
When Life bloomed from roots in
sacred ground. A love
was cradled safe and sound. A
dream was whispered through the rain. And
a
prayer rose from pain. In our hymns,
Cottolengo, you are grace. In
our Psalms, a light no night erases.
In our voices, your love still flows. God
gave us Cottolengo. Forever we
sing, Deo Gratias. Cottolengo,
the name we call home.
A shelter when the thunder roars. A Vase
where delicate
hearts are held. A dream that time can
never fold.
In our hymns, Cottolengo, you are grace.
In our Psalms, a light no night
erases. In our voices,
your love still flows. God gave us
Cottolengo.
Forever we sing, Deo Gratias.
We are the roses time can't fade. We are
the joy
Cottolengo dreamt. We are the love etched
in Cottolengo's
heart. Through every tear, joy, and
whispered prayer,
we still remain roses of Cottolengo. In our
hymns, Cottolengo, you are grace.
In our Psalms, a light no night
erases. In our voices,
your love still flows. God gave us
Cottolengo.
Forever we sing Deo Gratias.
Caritas Christi Urget Nos. With
Cottolengo, Deo Gratias
.